# ANDRE' GRADY

### Software Engineer

Puyallup, United States

(206)683-7969 grady.andre2@gmail.com

## LINKS

### <u>Portfolio</u>, <u>LinkedIn</u>

### **PROFILE**

I'm a dedicated junior developer who's extremely organized and a critical candidate who can successful manage multiple task. Also, committed to working as a collaborative and positive team member, striving to utilize my knowledge and expertise for optimal results.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

❖ Medical Assistant Lead, University of Washington	Nov 2021 — Present
<ul> <li>Lead a team of medical assistants to preform quality and effective COVID-19 testing.</li> </ul>	Scattle
• Train new medical assistants to properly gather patient information, prepare and collect swab specimen from patients.	
Preform quality checks on every patient vial using Microsoft excel.	
❖ Medical Assistant , University of Washington	Jul 2021 — Nov 2021 Seattle
Register/Check-in patient for Covid-19 testing	ocarrie
Engage with costumers with highest costumers service expectations.	
Collect specimen from patients while following proper PPE guidelines .	
<ul> <li>precisely enter patient information, and record patientinformation on testing vials</li> </ul>	
Customer Service Representative, City of Seattle	Jun 2020 — Jun 2021 Seattle
Gather and input patient information into SOLV software.	Seattle
Check-in / Register patients for COVID-19 testing.	
Record patient information onto specimen.	
Maintain exceptional costumer service with every patient.	
Follow PPE safety guidelines.	
EDUCATION	

University of Washingto	n	Jun 2022 — Nov 2022
Full-Stack Web Development Certific	ation	Seattle
Spokane Falls Communi	ty College	Aug 2018 — Aug 2019 Pullman
Pierce College at Puyallu	р	Aug 2017 — Aug 2018 Puyallup
Graham Kapowsin High High School Dibloma	School	Aug 2012 — Aug 2016 Graham

### **SKILLS**

MongoDB	MySQL
Bootstrap	jQuery
React	JavaScript
Git	HTML5
Node.js	CSS3